And it's fun to
discuss the city and its results, friends. Today, we will
discuss the results of ICICI Lombard's stock
and Lambi Pharma's quarterly results.
Friends,
what will be the target price, what will be the stop-loss, and what will be the
expected price tag for the
intermediate target range for tomorrow's internet retrading. We will also focus on this. So,
friends, let's
start the discussion with the same Alam Butt C Airtel B
Pharma stock. Friends,
if you want to do intraday trading,
then definitely join our Telegram channel, the
link of which is given in the description box,
and day trading by that name. If you
want to open a demat account, then you
must also click on the stock limit. This
stop-loss link will help you in applying for it.
So, friends, let's discuss the
city these days.
First of all, LMB's consolidated December 2019
results have come and net sales were Rs
31.14, producer affair 2.7 per cent
year-on-year. So, if you are an air base  But if you see,
their results have been quite good, net
sales have improved to around 100 crores
from last quarter which was
around 200 crores in the last year in 2012,
friends, the net profit for the quarter is
125 crores which is
25 percent for you, so definitely friends, and they
performed well on all parameters and their F-18 is
also improved to 367 crores in
December friends, by 12.5%, so definitely
friends, they have given a good result on every parameter
and from the running, also,
this liquor has increased by half, how much ten percent, so Rs. 14 and
40.8, 12.42 has also increased, so
friends, they have given a good result and as per the
price correction, it has already come
in LMB Pharma, so you
can check this information on the internet,
friends, let us see about the results of CNET,
CNET Standalone
December 2020 Net Sales End  Rupees to 212
producers, now one percent, so it has
definitely given a very good result, the
industry estimate has been tweeted and
Jio's net profit for the quarter is this, it has
also increased by five percent, so
definitely friends, the result of the stock is very good, the result is seen
at 79, the result has
improved by 80 percent and the thought is
on year to year basis and the earnings percentage
of increase has
doubled, so from every parameter,
somewhere
they have given a great result today, so this is an excellent
result, according to the long term goal, you can do
bike in this city, along with friends, if you
look at the share of ICICI Lombard, then let's see the
alarm but three pockets, you have six
point 663 shares and was 8313 card and the
growth report of ICICI Lombard is
9.20 percent growth on year
base effect, so definitely friends, the
revenue growth of ICICI Lombard is also very good and
industry expectation also  It was showing similar results
and its expected result is
also quite according to this, so a
good result has been given, apart from which
related operating profit has come, it has come
down on quarter to quarter basis,
but if you look at hair oil on year to year basis, then
it is of
support 6 percent, so definitely it is a
good result, if you
look at it in clear and on year to year basis and friends, the
operating margin is soft, down from
11.46 percent in December 2010,
point reduced, it has reduced a little,
so the consolidated net profit is 6.6 percent
and Ajay result, profit after tax
session margin tips lightly from 10.51
percent to 10.25%, so the result has weakened a little,
so we can say it is a flat result, a little
good result, so if you look from here, the
total income has increased, the net profit has
increased, this is in the near term,
but if we look at it on quarter to quarter basis, then a
little  There has been a decrease and the
stock is similar on a running basis, a very high
degree has been done in this poster and if you
look at Note 3, then there has been a very slight increase
and along with this there is a
slight effect on the Raavan Juliet margin, so
somewhere there is a mixed result,
Shahriyar can still go, don't worry, but it has already corrected
and as per the performance of the sector
and the growth aspects,
you should stay in the stock for the long term, so
friends, let us discuss at
what level should we buy, sell
or hold, so
friends, if we look at the short term perspective,
we first look at it from a three-month perspective,
friends, if you have bought someone's treatment perspective
and the stock, then place a stoploss of around 14
48 and the
target on the upside is 1626, listen again friends, the
stoploss is 1448 and the
target on the upside is 1626, if you want to talk then buy
around 1490  If the labels are there then do it
around 1480, brother, put a stop loss of 1448 and
take a target of 1526 and here friends,
if
we think of an intraday target like 84, then it may be
interesting, some profit
booking can be seen
in the morning session, but after that there are
chances of improvement, so I suggest you to use the stop loss theorem here
that
after getting some off work results in the morning, you should go
straight into it after 10:00 and only after that you should
make this circulation, but if you
look at it carefully, then definitely you can click on it
and the volume is also fine, there is no
problem, a good
candle is seen forming in the last also, friends, if
we have
seen the first copy of Laddu Pharma after talking halfway, friends, if you wake up in the morning and
see first of all, there is a lot of positive energy, there has been a lot of
correction, it has reached 1034, the
level which used to be at 1150, it has
given a lot of correction from there and it is also a
decent protein  So
if you click on it at the current level, then
book it around 1030, put a stop loss of ₹
19, friends, of ₹70 and the levels on the upper side will be
around 1120, labels are visible
in Teen Mat, if friends, you are doing intraday
trading, then if you
look at the target accordingly, then my suggestion is,
hey brother, do it and book profit on the upper side around 1040, 1050
and the
stoploss on the lower side is 1010, stock broker, so
put a stoploss of 1010, you do it around 1038, brother,
you have to book profit at 1055, so
from here you can get two to three percent
interest, friends, if you
look at the set, then even today people are
extracting it clearly and according to the
promise it is showing, hence, if
you look at Teen Mat, then it is clearly indicating
around 68k, so whenever RS ​​is around 370, then the
volume mute is being removed on this side, so
Definitely friends, this upset
can show a target of three hundred and fifty from here,
but friends, do not forget one thing that
if you are looking at the last one month, then
in one month you have already seen a side
moment in it, from about 1046 it has
reached 1273, that is, more than
fifteen percent already.
As you saw in the selection, the
results of the technology giant Infosys were also very
good, besides that the stock fell,
however, it can go up in the morning trading,
so if you
can buy it for the current hour from morning then like it, otherwise
wait for the correction to come in it, at the current level, what I suggest is that
if you want to buy, then
buy it at about 1101 level, right now it is
coming very high, it is on the upward path, there can be
short term profit in it, but
in the long term there are chances of a little loss, so
definitely friends, you can buy good
quality honey, but
like 11 Shukla and
your target  Those 13 balls will be received and
targets up to 14 years can be seen
from the stone. Friends, your perspective will have to be a little
long term and
you have to set the stoploss of 1000, so friends,
focus on the stoploss target that has been suggested and follow me, it
goes by the name Trading Balls
on Telegram, Twitter and Facebook.
Do read the disclaimer because the share market
is saying Rus and we only
make it for educational purpose, we have
nothing to do with investment, so
friends, do read it. Thank you friends.